websuccess4you.biz 2016-10-29

# 

Plug-In Profit Site Privacy Policy 

Last Updated: January 25, 2006 

PlugInProfitSite.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will not sell, barter, rent or share your personal information to third parties, except as described in this privacy statement. 

PlugInProfitSite.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site http://www.pluginprofitsite.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Stone Evans at privacy@pluginprofitsite.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe here. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

How we gather information from users 

The information collected from our users it used for the purpose of building their website as described in the Plug-In Profit Site signup page. You will be asked for your name, e-mail address, affiliate ID#'s, domain name and hosting account username and password. Once your website is setup, you will also receive follow-up training emails at the email address provided in your application. You may opt-out of these emails at any time. Like most Web sites, PlugInProfitSite.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences. 

If you choose to use our referral service (located inside the Plug-In Profit Site member's area) to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. PlugInProfitSite.com does not store this information and only uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email on your behalf. 

What we do with the information we collect 

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone. 

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually. 

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on PlugInProfitSite.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by PlugInProfitSite.com and other topics we think you might find of interest through the email you provide upon signing up for the Plug-In Profit Site service. You can opt-out of these emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link located in each email or by contacting privacy@pluginprofitsite.com with your request. 

Part of the process of signing up for the Plug-In Profit Site service includes signing up for 5 affiliate programs and a hosting service. SFI, Success University, Empowerism and Host4Profit each send a confirmation email to the referring affiliate which contains the name and e-mail address you used to create those accounts. This information is not used by PlugInProfitSite.com. 

Personally Identifiable Information collected by PlugInProfitSite.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other service related communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. we will share personally identifiable information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. In such a case, all Plug-In Profit Site members will be notified by email and given the option to opt-out of future communication if desired. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements 

PlugInProfitSite.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a PlugInProfitSite.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through PlugInProfitSite.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. PlugInProfitSite.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. 

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. PlugInProfitSite.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. 

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, or in testimonials that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of PlugInProfitSite.com and this policy. The Plug-In Profit Site forum is located on a third-party website. 

Children 

PlugInProfitSite.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe PlugInProfitSite.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below. 

Contacting us 

We can be reached by contacting: 

privacy@pluginprofitsite.com 

19009 Preston Road, Suite 215-209 Dallas, TX 75252 

If you are a current Plug-In Profit Site member and wish to make changes to your account information you can do so by logging into your member's area here: http://www.pluginprofitsite.com/account 

If you are a current Plug-In Profit Site member and wish to close your account you can do so by logging into your member's area here: http://www.pluginprofitsite.com/remove 

All other Plug-In Profit Site account resources can be obtained by logging in here: http://www.pluginprofitsite.com/login 

Changes to this policy 

PlugInProfitSite.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

Security 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at privacy@pluginprofitsite.com 

Governing law 

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Texas law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Dallas, Texas. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us. 

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Dallas, Texas, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so. 

PlugInProfitSite.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Texas. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
